NUTTHANUN WIRIYAJAREANPANIT

NONTHABURI | +66(0)84 616 9779, | nutthanun.w94@gmail.com

Professional Summary

Working as a System supporter and Project manager assistance in Customer Support department for almost 4 years with high communication skills, analysis skills, and well solving unexpected problem skills. Be able to conduct negotiation with the vendor to achieve the best way of solution of the projects. Highly expertise with the experience of BPO (Business Process Outsourcing) processes and responsible for 400+ HCs, planning manpower, operation work process, strategic planning and transformation project improvement.

Achievements

- Succeed for replacement CRM system project to Salesforce.com within budgetary and constraints.
- Set up policies and contract management for BPO (Business Process Outsourcing) vendors transfer projects with twice vendors within timeline constraints.

Experience

Customer Support strategy & Transformation Lead LINE MAN Wongnai

07/2021 to Current

- Shaped the company's overall business strategy and presented projects related to customer support under BPO which has more than 300HC+ to achieve KPI/OKR goals smoothly
- Was a main workforce to gather the requirements for CRM replacement project in order to impose and improve KPI/OKR of the team
- · Consolidated issue, impact, and insight data analysis to find root cause for improvement.
- Set up flow and timeline for project improvement of Customer Support team according to SOP and business policies
- Controlled expenditures by regulating change requests and project activities to decrease overruns and delays.
- Led and motivated project team to meet and exceed project KPIs.
- Communicated progress updates to various stakeholders to secure further funding for project activities.
- Reported project status and financial updates to stakeholders and collected feedback.
- Reviewed performance against targets, appropriately identifying and managing risks and opportunities.
- Applied successful project management techniques to enable project delivery within budgetary and time constraints.

Customer Support Strategy Project/System Coordinator LINE MAN Wongnai

02/2021 to 07/2021

- Coordinated with product manager, staff, and internal outsource for project planning sessions and ensured that project deadlines are met properly
- Analyze project progress and, when necessary, adapt scope, timelines, and costs to achieve maximum benefit
- · Assign roles and tasks to dedicated team members, based on individual strengths and abilities
- · Build the skill sets of individual team members and capture overall learnings for the company
- · Coordinated with accountant about payment process to allocate limited business budget productively

Customer Support Supervisor LINE MAN Wongnai

09/2020 to 02/2021

- Managed and handled team of customer support agents that have more than 30
- HCs to achieve the same goal most productively and effectively
- Planned and proceeded the overall operation of customer support team to meet KPI/PKR
- Always be prepared to conduct as a team consultant Scheduled and managed manpower in each shift to be able to handle several cases which are related to customer service productively
- · Taken good care of team member's well-being to achieve attrition rate OKR

Senior Customer Support Executive

05/2020 to 09/2020

Wongnai Media

- Planned and proceeded the overall operation of customer support team to meet OKR
- Analyzed and resolved the problems related to customer
- Updated new product knowledge as up to date within the team to work effectively

- Scheduled and managed manpower in each shift to operate productive work
- Prepared product or service reports by collecting and analyzing customer information

Customer Support Executive

06/2019 to 05/2020

Wongnai Media

- Identified and assessed customers' needs to achieve satisfaction
- Conducted as a supporter, adviser, and solver for customer; giving advice and finding solution
- Achieved productivity achievement and QA achievement Built sustainable relationships of trust through open and interactive communication
- Handled complaints, provide appropriate solutions and alternatives within the time limits and follow up to ensure resolution

Customer Experience

06/2018 to 06/2019

ServisHero

- Resolved customer complaints via phone, email, mail or social media
- Resolved product or service problems by clarifying the customer's complaint; determining the cause of the
 problem; selecting and explaining the best solution to solve the problem; expediting correction or adjustment;
 following up to ensure resolution
- Recommended potential products or services to management by collecting customer information and analyzing customer needs
- · Identified and assessed customers' needs to achieve satisfaction

Core Qualifications

- Salesforce.com
- BPO management
- · Process improvement
- Requirements gathering
- Customer needs analysis
- Customer service expert
- · Customer support needs assessment
- Call centre experience
- Time management

- Google Workspace
- Adaptability
- Leadership
- Strong Communication Skills
- Problem Solving Skills
- Ability to Multitask
- Fast Learner
- Teamwork
- Decision Making

Education

Bachelor of Science and Technology: Information and Communication Technology

May 2018

University of the Thai Chamber of Commerce

GPA: 3.31, Second Class Honors

Google sheet Advance, POE Club

September 2021

Referrence

- Miss. Chompunut Yeamnam
- From Head of Customer & Operations Support, LINE MAN Wongnai
- Email: kaopun@lmwn.com
- Tel: +66 (0)82 561 4456